( silence )
( car engine )
( radio chatter )
( radio chatter continues )
Pat : Shit .
Sam .
- ( Sam groans ) - Pat : Sam , wake up .
What 's wrong ?
( whispers ) Fuck .
What 'd you do , Tiger ?
- When did we crash ? - Sam : You tell us , asshole .
I guess I fell asleep .
Yeah ...
with the engine running .
( phone vibrates )
Fully charged .
Did you kill the battery too ?
You hear the radio ?
There 's a skating rink about 11 miles from here .
Big parking lot .
Ice skating or rollerskating ?
Just says they 're open .
Why ?
Reece : Hockey players whoop more ass .
I don 't know , dude . I 've seen some pretty bad-ass roller skaters .
At 7 : 00 AM ?
All right , I 'll come with .
( shutter clicks )
- Sam ? - Sam : Tad .
Tad : Awesome .
Hey , I work nights , but I 'll catch up with you guys for breakfast .
- Okay . - I 'm in 2-R up the stairs .
Just crash wherever . Uh , park in the side lot .
Rear doors tight to the walls so no one steals your shit .
All right .
Yeah ?
Sam : These all have mushrooms .
This dude 's legit .
Reece : Why ? ' Cause he wakes up at 5 : 00 in the morning
to put jizz in his hair ?
Tiger : Mm ...
No . He 's true .
Ree-Ree .
Who you callin ' ?
Is that your business ?
I get the bills .
I 'm going to bed .
We 're gonna drink .
♪ One , two , three , four , one , two , three , four ♪
♪ Legalize ♪
( record player static )
( Pat sighs )
Mornin ' .
Hello .
You were the first to fall asleep ?
Okay , I 'm with the Ain 't Rights from Washington , D.C.
Uh , technically , we 're from Arlington .
Tad : Nice . Uh , and this is for Seaside HCFM .
Not for the zine ?
Tad : I 'll do a print version for that ,
but this will run on our college station .
Uh , if that 's cool .
Sam : Yeah .
So , you guys working on anything new ?
Sam : Mm , yeah . A few songs .
Maybe enough for , like , a seven inch .
Tad : Sweet . Will you actually press one ?
Yeah , if we can afford it .
Tad : Yeah , no , I really dig the analog style .
Uh , which brings me to the fact
you guys are hard to find .
Why no social media presence ?
Reece : That 's because booking more shows ,
selling more records would blow .
It 's not hard rock .
No one wants to starve , but ...
when you take it all virtual , you lose ...
the texture .
- What do you mean " texture " ? - Just ... you gotta be there .
The music is for effect .
It 's time and aggression ...
Technical wizardry .
And it 's shared live ...
and then it 's over .
The energy can 't last .
Unless you 're Iggy Pop .
Yeah , well good for him , but I don 't think I wanna
be in my 70 's still listening to Minor Threat .
- But Tiger does . - I won 't live to be 70 , so ...
( Sam and Tad laugh )
Okay , so , uh , this is a good seg
into one of my traditions .
Uh , for each of you , name your desert island band .
Only one ?
Reece : If I were to say Black Sabbath ,
would I get Ozzy and Dio ?
No caveats . Just name the band .
Okay .
Misfits .
No , The Damned .
- Um ... - Tiger : Oh , fuck it . Misfits .
- Sam : Poison Idea . - Cro-Mags .
Tad : That 's a good one also .
Reece : Why don 't you say something , dude ?
Tiger : What about Steely Dan ?
- Hm . No , Candlebox . - He 's a juggalo .
- Uh ... uh ... - Tiger : Britney Spears ?
Hey ... hey , you ... you ... you 're gonna
- edit this , right ? - I can chop it up a bit .
- Tiger : Oh , you should let it go raw , man . - Um , when is this gonna air ?
Like , maybe we should plug the show ?
Yeah . Um ...
My last show at The Muni Center didn 't end well .
Uh , lots of vomit , some fecal matter .
County commissioner got wind and pulled my permit .
You guys were already en route .
No , you gotta give us a kill fee .
- We went 90 miles out of our way . - I 've got a backup lined up .
Um , lunch , 50 % cut on the door ,
and you guys would headline .
Is anyone still on the bill ?
No .
( punk music playing )
♪ I 'm always broke ♪
♪ And I 'm alone ♪
♪ I ask myself ♪
♪ What have I become ? ♪
♪ I must be drunk ♪
♪ I must be stoned ♪
♪ I ask myself ♪
♪ What have I become ? ♪
Turn that shit off .
I gave you my cut .
Uh , the house got theirs , but I didn 't ...
Split four ways , it 's six bucks each .
$ 6.87 .
.88 if you just round up ...
You dip-shit , fashion punk clown motherfucker .
- Christ . - Now easy there , jiu-jitsu .
Yeah . We don 't wanna go to jail , too .
I think you just ended this tour . - Fuck yes . Let 's call it .
Sam : All right , so we 'd have to beeline to DC .
We have enough for one tank .
We 'd have to siphon the rest of the way .
Reece : That 's not a problem .
We got rice and beans .
We can head up north . Take the 80 all the way .
What the fuck you doing , man ?
Let me call my cousin .
I can get you guys a solid gig .
Where ? Here ?
Scene is dead .
You 'd have to dip down closer to Portland .
( phone vibrates )
Tiger : I say we just gank his vinyl .
All right , so all set .
Uh , matinée tomorrow .
Door 's at 1 : 00 , you guys are on at 3 : 00 .
- I texted the addy . - Sam : How much ?
Uh , $ 350 .
Minus your tab .
And , um , just so you know , it 's mostly boots and braces down there .
Skins ? There 's some at every show .
What ? D.M.S. ? Sharp ?
Uh , right-wing , or technically ultra-left ,
but not affiliated .
- And your cousin 's cool ? - Tad : Yeah , yeah .
Uh , don 't talk politics , but stick with Daniel .
I 'd tag along , but he and his girl are coming here to crash .
Gotta vacuum and shit .
So they 're not , like , burning crosses
or anything , right ? Like , we just play rock ?
Uh , I 'd play your earlier stuff .
Heavier stuff .
I usually keep the originals , but since this one never happened ...
Can I still run that interview ?
Yeah .
What station is it on ?
Uh , FM 85.5 .
Breakfast With Champions .
- Thanks . - Reece : Yo , Tad-pole ...
I 'm sorry I almost obliterated you , man .
( car engine starts )
Not a problem .
Take it easy .
At least the dude can draw .
Yeah , it 's pretty sweet .
Yo , Pat ...
you know , there 's something I 've never told people ...
or anyone , for that matter .
What ?
- ( farts ) - ( all laugh )
Was that real ? Ew !
Tiger : Open your window .
Sam : Good .
( punk music playing )
( dog barking )
You Tad 's friends ?
Uh , he sent us .
Are you Cousin Dan ?
Daniel : Daniel .
You guys look hammered .
Tiger : One night at Tad 's will do that to you .
And if your girl 's gonna be crashing ...
Don 't mention that .
- Okay , I was just ... - Yeah , no worries whatsoever .
Just shut the fuck up about it him and me and her . - Yeah .
Drummer ? Drummer ?
Using the house kit or are you using yours ?
I 'll use mine .
Okay . Load in 's here .
Sam : That 's bullshit .
" Aren 't Rights " ? Yeah .
♪ Demon of dark ♪
♪ Angel of black ♪
♪ Pure hatred burns ♪
♪ Start your attack ♪
Stage rest in here .
Don 't block the hallway .
The owner doesn 't fuck around with the fire codes .
Sound check in 15 .
- You 're on in 20 . - Got it .
♪ Darklord imperial slaves ♪
♪ Slaves , slaves , slaves ♪
Pat : Hey , Tiger ...
are you okay ?
Yeah , I 'm fine .
Sam : Are these guys not creeps ?
- ( phone vibrates ) - They run a tight ship .
Except it 's a U-boat .
Hey , y 'all ... I got a dumb idea .
Stagehand : Where 'd you say the power supply was ?
It 's like a mini-transformer ...
Testing , testing one , two .
- Meow . - Stagehand : Got it !
Pat : There 's no guitar .
( microphone feedback )
- Or not . - This was your fucking idea .
You back out now , I tell them you 're Jewish .
Go .
Evening , ladies and gentlemen .
We are the Ain 't Rights ,
or the Aren 't Rights .
Either one ...
two , three , four !
♪ Punk ain 't no religious cult ♪
♪ Punk means thinking for yourself ♪
♪ You ain 't hardcore 'cause you spike your hair ♪
♪ When a jock still lives inside your head ♪
♪ Nazi punks , Nazi punks , Nazi punks , fuck off ! ♪
♪ If you 've come to fight , get outta here ♪
♪ You ain 't no better than the bouncers ♪
♪ We ain 't trying to be police ♪
♪ When you ape the cops , it ain 't anarchy ♪
♪ Nazi punks , Nazi punks , Nazi punks , fuck off ! ♪
♪ Ten guys jump one , what a man ♪
♪ You fight each other , the police state wins ♪
♪ Stab your backs when you trash our halls ♪
♪ Trash a bank if you 've got real balls ♪
♪ You still think swastikas look cool ♪
♪ The real Nazis run your schools ♪
♪ They 're coaches , businessmen , and cops ♪
♪ In a real fourth Reich , you 'll be the first to go ♪
♪ Nazi punks , Nazi punks , Nazi punks , fuck off ! ♪
♪ Don 't you know you 'll be the first to go ♪
♪ Unless you think ? ♪
Crowd : Fuck off ! Come on !
Thank you . That was a cover .
What should we do next ?
Sam : Coronary .
Tiger : This one 's a treat .
( punk music plays )
( classical score playing )
( thrash metal music playing )
♪ Infiltration push reserves ♪
♪ Encircle the front lines ♪
♪ Supreme art of strategy ♪
♪ Playing on the minds ♪
- Sam : What happened to fire code ? - Yeah , sorry guys .
We have to make room for the headliner .
Cowcatcher , right ?
Big Justin : Yes . You gotta clear out , okay ?
Here you are .
- Thank you . - Big Justin : And it 's all there . And you guys follow me , okay ?
All right .
I 'll get you one more two liter for the road .
Okay , come on .
- You all right with that ? - I 'll be careful . I understand .
- Aw , shit . My phone ... - Pat : What ?
My phone . I ... I 'll catch up with ...
- I got you . - Sam : Thanks .
Excuse me , y 'all .
( phone vibrates )
Oh shit .
- Can you call the cops ? - Guitarist : Fuck that .
Hey , stop !
- What the fuck ? - ( Sam yelps )
I told you to follow .
No !
Go , go , go !
Uh , yeah . I ... I ... I guess I am . I don 't know .
There 's been a ... there 's been a stabbing !
She ... Whoa ! Whoa !
Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa .
- ( overlapping chatter , yelps ) - Goddamn it !
- They didn 't lock the door . - You didn 't lock the door !
No ! Don 't talk and don 't touch them !
Stay put !
It 's fine .
- What the fuck happened ? - Just give me a minute !
Something terrible . Stay with them .
♪ Be dead , friend from above ♪
♪ When darkness falls ♪
♪ Descend into my sights ♪
♪ Your fallen walls ♪
- Okay . - Sam : Oh , shit !
- It 's okay . Don 't worry , don 't worry . Get back inside . - ( phone rings )
What the fuck is going on ?
Gabe : Up . In the room .
Hey ! Go ! Go !
Up the stairs . It 's okay . Let 's go .
Just go . Come on , guys .
- Tiger : Shit . - Gabe : It 's okay .
- ( ringing continues ) - Oh , what the fuck , man ?
Gabe : It 's okay . It 's fine .
Turn that PA down .
- You didn 't lock the door . - You were right there !
- Big Justin : Until I wasn 't ! - Gabe : Quiet !
Hello ? Woman : This is emergency services .
Yeah , we got cut off . I was calling to report a stabbing .
( breathes heavily )
( mumbling )
Gabe : Yes .
Yes , ma 'am .
( door opens )
Did you call Darcy ?
He 's on his way . He knows about that ...
not this .
- You can 't keep us here , man . You gotta let us go . - Gabe : We 're not keeping you .
You 're just staying .
You 're up . - What the fuck is that supposed to mean ?
Just relax !
Everyone , just relax .
Cops are coming .
( door closes )
- See how easy that is ? - Motherfucker !
- Look what you did ! - Amber , chill the fuck out !
- Yes . Please . - ( Amber sobs )
( door opens )
- Darcy here ? - Not yet .
I need $ 600 cash .
You just signed out $ 350 .
Somebody 's dead .
Still gotta keep the books .
What else do you need ?
A true believer .
How ' bout two ?
- Maybe she 's not dead . - ( scoffs )
Sam : I 'm just saying .
Like , there 's not a lot of blood .
You know , so , like , maybe she 's just ...
and who are we to say that she 's ...
- ( body thumps ) - Sam : Oh , shit !
( all groan and gasp )
Big Justin : Come on , man .
- What are you doing ? - ( grunts )
- ( shudders ) - Tiger : The fuck , man ?
There it is .
Oh , my God .
Reece : We gotta go . We gotta fucking go right now .
Now we didn 't see shit .
We ... we ... we were so drunk .
All right , just wait , okay ?
Cops are on the way .
Gabe : Above and beyond , gentlemen .
You need me to do it ?
- Twin 1 : Nope . - Won 't even be the first time .
- ( siren wails ) - Hurry up .
- Twin 1 : Go . - ( both twins grunt )
All right , that 's it .
Okay , let me see it .
The knife .
It 's an inch too short for felony possession ,
so you don 't have to worry about the ...
Actually , give me that money back .
Twin 2 : What ?
It 's like vouchers and shit .
We 'll hold it for you . Come on .
If you do any time , we 'll double it .
Now talk to ' em .
- You the victim ? - Twin 1 : Yes , officer .
Officer : Kneel down .
Both of you , ankles crossed .
Gabe : That 's the owner .
I called him too .
Darcy : All right , let 's give them some room to work , folks .
Are you the owner ?
Darcy : Yes , ma 'am .
( knocking )
Cowcatcher , clear out .
Hey , where are the cops ?
- Gabe : Get your stuff , man . - Tiger : What about us ?
Amber : What are you doing ?
We 're sorting it out . Just hang tight , Amber .
Your set was pretty good .
What ?
What was the name of your second to last song ?
Uh ...
To ... Toxic Evolution .
It 's fucking hard , man .
That 's the one I did her to .
( breathes heavily )
All right , he 's got six bullets ...
- For real ? - ... if we all go at once ...
- Tiger : Guys , hold off a sec . - For what ?
- Sam : We haven 't done anything ! - It doesn 't matter .
- Okay . - They 're called cartridges .
The bullet is the part that enters your brain
if you keep talking shit .
And this gun only has five cartridges , not six ,
'cause they 're big as fuck and only five fit the cylinder .
So , please shut the fuck up and don 't test me .
Reece , you 're making it worse .
We sit and we wait .
And we die ?
Not if you sit and you wait .
It 's just the one to 911 at 3 : 45
and then mine was at 3 : 47 . - You called ?
- 911 called back and I answered . - Be clear .
Who else knows besides ... You said Daniel 's cousin ?
Tad .
There was a text from him last night with our address ,
but he doesn 't know anything .
Except who they are , where they are ...
maybe where they 're supposed to be next .
Fuck .
Check emails .
They played their set to the crowd .
Then we 'll assume the wide world knows
and they 'll be tracking that .
Give it to me .
I was trying to buy some time
and contain this until we could ...
Contain ?
It was pretty rapid fire .
I appreciate your initiative and we all love Werm .
He 's a brother .
And you might have visited him in prison .
Makes a difference .
Now we 're all in the stew
for an impulsive act ,
for a selfish act ,
under my roof .
You see a way out of this ?
Gabe : For them ?
No .
We still have to find one .
Okay . This is good .
( metal music starts playing )
No guns .
You have a " No trespassing " sign posted at the residence ?
We got " Beware of dogs . "
That 's better .
Does anyone even know we 're in here ?
No one who cares . Tad ?
- I think we go . - I think we go too .
- Big Justin : The next person that moves ... - ( knocking )
Gabe : Everyone okay ?
Just about .
Gabe ?
- Gabe : Yeah . Open up . - No !
- Where are the cops ? - Big Justin : Okay ...
do you want me to open the door ,
or do you want me to blow your fucking head off ?
- Back the fuck off ! - Gabe : What 's going on ?
They 're trying to run at me !
Gabe : Do not shoot them !
Big Justin : You know what ? That 's on them .
Where are the cops ?
Gabe : Give them the gun !
Say again ?
Gabe : It 's over !
Give them the gun .
Okay , I told you they just tried to run at me ...
Gabe : Then take the bullets out !
Just hand it over now !
Do not shoot them !
Is Darcy here ?
- Gabe : He is . - Darcy : I am .
Gentlemen , I 'm the owner . Okay , why the fuck didn 't you just tell me ?
Darcy : Truly sorry about this .
Playing catch-up here myself .
They 're playing a fucking show .
Pat : Uh ...
thank you , but ...
we open the door for the police ,
or we keep the bullets .
Uh , the cartridges .
Darcy : I 've got no problem with that .
Okay , I handed them the gun .
- I 'm gonna head out now . - No , you 're not .
- Let him open the door . - Hang on .
- No , he gave us the gun , he gave us the gun ... - Big Justin : Nobody is ...
letting me do anything . I gave you the goddamn gun , okay ?
- Darcy : So how are we doing ? - He 's right .
Pat , do the math .
Where are the police ? - Darcy : It takes a while out here .
- Stay back . - Darcy : Just want to make sure that no one else gets hurt
in the meantime .
- Big Justin : Okay , I gave you the damn gun ... - ( screams )
- Tiger ! - ( grunts and screams )
- Reece : Get him down ! - Darcy : Justin ?
Reece : Get him down !
( grunts and screams )
Darcy : What 's happening ?
( grunts )
Shh !
- ( banging on door ) - Darcy : Justin ?
- ( grunts ) - Shouldn 't have locked the door .
Shit . Sam !
Get the bullets !
All right , load the gun .
- Darcy : How 's it going in there ? - Big Justin : Not good !
Fine , but we would rather wait for the police !
Darcy : Justin ?
Reece : He 's fine ...
but he 's gonna wait too !
Understood , gentlemen .
Hold tight .
You think they know ?
I think they 're smarter than you !
Darcy ...
Man .
I apologize .
We 'll do it here . Stage it up the road . - Okay .
- Pat : Hey , what was that gonzo shit , man ? - So in a tournament ,
I snap his arm or he taps out and we all go get burgers .
- Snap it . - Come on .
Look , we 've got the gun .
- Why don 't we just let him ... - Wait , wait . I don 't want it .
All right ? I don 't ... I don 't feel good with it .
Who wants it ?
- Not me . - Sam : Hm ?
- No . I can 't shoot . - I can .
No , not you .
- Then fucking keep it . - Reece : Keep it , Sam .
I 'll take it when I 'm up .
When I let go ...
what are you gonna do ?
( grunts )
Butt-fuck everyone in the room .
You 're gonna sit criss-cross applesauce .
Say it .
I 'm gonna sit criss-cross apple sau ...
Nice .
Now lean against the chair .
Hey , is there another way out of here ?
No .
You fed ' em yet today ?
It doesn 't matter .
They 're professionals .
Darcy : You might lose a couple by morning
Maybe a bunch .
Clark : Like I said , they 're pros .
They earn .
You 'll be compensated .
Christ . How many people are on that list ?
Clark : It 's 1,200 for a prospect ,
two for a bait dog .
No studs , no champs unless you wanna pay
20 grand a head .
Darcy : This might cost you your livelihood , Clark .
As long as it doesn 't cost me mine , you 're covered .
( metal music playing )
There are gonna be cops , so clean up the residence .
Maybe leave a roach in an ashtray .
Put Daniel on that door and bring the van around .
Shit .
The keys .
They 're with them , I guess .
- I don 't know . - We need them .
I got a ton of shit to do .
Go on .
This is a fire hazard .
I wouldn 't put Daniel on the door .
Fine . Plenty to do .
Where 's Daniel ?
He stepped out . I 'm covering .
Everything okay ?
Meet me at the utility shed .
( engine starts )
Darcy : This a new ride ?
Yeah .
Just turning it over .
I think it 's getting choked .
Wrong filter .
- She 's a beaut . - What 's up ?
Need some of the squad .
Red laces only .
- Tonight ? - Darcy : Now .
The list .
This is everybody who knows ?
Yeah . Including the band .
Knows what ?
Manageable .
From here on out , not a single name gets added
unless they have red laces .
There 's 80 people in there .
You plus four .
Give Gabe the keys in case we have to play valet .
We 're losing light .
- Tiger : You got it ? - Sam : Yeah .
Whoa , watch out !
That could be asbestos .
- Tiger : It 's not asbestos . - You don 't have a phone , do you ?
They took it .
- Hers too . - I 'm gonna search her , okay ?
Sam : Careful . That one could be a live wire .
Tiger : It 's a speaker wire .
Sam : What 'd you find ?
Pat : Uh ...
" Fleisch Wolf " ?
Sam : Uh ... fleisch means ...
uh , flesh .
Or meat .
Like a fleisch salad . It 's German .
So " Meat Wolf " ?
Sam : Yeah .
( banging )
This shit 's solid .
- Great . - Pat : There 's nothing here .
Okay . Empty out your pockets .
Come search me , faggot .
Just shoot him .
Come on .
Can I get up ?
Reece : On the chair .
Slowly . Slowly .
Turn ' em out .
Come on , man . Other one .
Oh fuck .
Good call .
Turn it out , for fuck 's sake .
( Big Justin rustling )
Pat : What is that ? Give that to me .
- Hand it over ! - ( phone beeps , snaps )
- ( Sam gasps ) - Big Justin : Oops .
- Wait , was that a phone ? - ( Sam gasps )
- ( music stops ) - Pat : Oh , shit . Point it ... point it at the door .
Point the gun at the door . - Sam : Maybe it 's the police . It 's a raid .
- Amber : Are you serious ? - Pat : Shh !
- Sam : Fuck off , Ilsa ! - Reece : Yo , quiet , okay ? Justin , don 't move .
- Pat : Point the gun ... - Reece : Nobody move .
- Pat : Now if we get all behind ... - Reece : Nobody talk !
Careful now .
Smoke this .
Big Justin : Deal .
And if the cherry does something that you don 't like ...
shoot .
Reece : Thank you , Amber .
Get comfortable .
Sam : Pretty smart for a Nazi .
Amber : I 'm not a Nazi .
Pat : How do you fall for this shit ?
Amber : Let 's just say the people who were gonna hurt me weren 't white .
Pat : Any of them women ?
Amber : It 's a problem where I grew up .
- Reece : Guys . - Pat : What about tonight ?
I think we got a white people ... - Reece : Guys ! Shh .
Amber : Oh , fuck you .
( overlapping chatter )
( cheers and applause )
- It looks like we tripped our main . - ( crowd groans )
Our back-up gennie is fired up , but we 're gonna to have to
call it a day and do some troubleshooting .
- ( crowd groans louder ) - We 'll try again on Sunday .
No door charge .
Hell , free drinks from 2 : 00 to 4 : 00 . - ( crowd cheers )
( car engine starts )
( phone vibrates )
( phone ringing )
Those of you attending the racial advocacy workshop on Wednesday ,
assume it 's on unless you hear otherwise .
And remember ...
this is a movement , not a party .
- ( cheers and applause ) - All right .
Stay safe ! Godspeed .
Who hasn 't smoked yet ?
All right , you guys are gonna come with me .
( cabinets open , close )
You 're not worried they 'll talk ?
They 've got priorities .
Tell them the party is on us if they hole up for a couple of days .
Put this fire out first .
Grove Street ?
My dope nigger stamps in case one of these meat-heads
gets booked for possession .
All right .
Let 's get y 'all somewhere safe .
Sam : Treasure ?
Daylight . Underneath .
( banging )
They 're moving our gear .
( knocking )
- Yes ? - Darcy : Gentlemen ?
We 're loading you out .
Are there cops here ?
Darcy : They 've come and gone . It got a little complicated .
We 're so fucked .
Darcy : Uh , I 'm getting hoarse .
Can you hear me if I speak at this volume ?
- Yeah . - Yes .
Darcy : Good .
Um ...
and can we please elect just one voice ?
Yes .
Darcy : Okay . Now , you 're trapped .
That 's not a threat . It 's a fact .
Well , we have a loaded gun .
That 's also just a fact .
Darcy : Oh , we have plenty more guns on hand .
We just want you out .
Not harmed .
Now , the firearm you have is not registered .
I wanted it out of the picture before the authorities arrived ,
but you refused , so here we are .
- Bullshit . - Yeah .
Here we are .
Darcy : Oh , I do apologize for my associates . They panicked .
- Yeah , no shit ! Man , we 're ... - Darcy : Listen ! Listen !
No one is trying to wipe the slate clean .
Whatever you saw or did is no longer my concern .
You tell whoever you want whatever you want .
All I ask is that you understand you were held here
for your own safety before you were released .
Okay .
Yes . Thank you .
But just ...
just to be clear ...
the police are coming back ?
Darcy : They 've come and gone .
Well , that 's what concerns us , man !
Darcy : I just want that gun out of the picture .
Okay .
- Reece : Careful , man . - Sorry .
- What do we do ? - We dig through the fucking floor .
While we just wait ?
They could shoot us at any time . - Yeah , but they haven 't .
How do we even know that they have guns ?
- They have guns . - No question .
We 're gonna trust you ?
- We 've got zero leverage . - Ask for a phone ...
- for the gun . - All right .
- What about him ? - Yeah , I mean , the minute we give it up ,
- what if he just , like , attacks ? - Then I 'll wrap him up .
Okay .
- So we see what they think ? - Mm-hmm .
All right .
Uh , we 'll give you the gun for a cell phone .
Darcy : Sorry , no .
- Okay , well , how about a registered firearm ? - Darcy : Funny .
Justin , you alive and well ?
- I 'm alive . - Darcy : Okay , good .
Gentlemen , I hope you appreciate the situation .
Things have gone south , no doubt .
But you know if you don 't hand over that gun ,
it won 't end well .
You see ...
for all I know , I ... I come to my place of business
and there is an out of town band
locked in a room with an unregistered firearm .
- Oh , come on ! - Darcy : And somebody 's hurt inside there
and maybe there 's a hostage , too !
So what do I do ?
Am I within my rights to intervene ?
Should I kick down the door and start shooting ?
- ( sniffles ) - Darcy : Or ...
can we just remove the guns from the equation ?
These are my questions .
You 've got 30 seconds to answer .
Okay , hold on . Hold on .
Great . Anyone got any smart ideas ?
Justin , get on the floor .
Get on the fuckin ' floor right now . Go .
All right . Sam , come around here .
Slowly , I want you to take the gun from me . - Sam : Okay .
- Reece : You got it ? - Sam : Got it .
Okay . Nice and easy .
Play nice , and I 'll be nice .
Sam : Please .
Don 't do anything .
- This is fuckin ' retarded . - Pat : No one 's saying it isn 't ,
but we either hand over the gun or we open fire with it .
- I vote for that . - You don 't have a vote , okay ?
- ( scoffs ) - I mean we 're taking chances either way , so ...
Tiger : So we 're fuckin ' dead , guys .
At least this way , we find out
if all we 're doing now is buying time .
- For them . - Reece : Amen .
At this point , I 'm just fucking curious .
Okay ... we 'll give you the gun .
But we 're gonna keep the ammo .
Darcy : Fine . Safer for everyone .
All right , let 's move this fucking couch .
Sam : Okay .
( breathes heavily )
All right , keep still .
Okay , stand back !
Darcy : You 've got it .
( breathes heavily )
Here we go .
Darcy : May I approach ?
Pat : No !
No . I 'm gonna throw it .
Careful . It was a gift .
- They 're killing us ! - Keep the gun !
( screaming and grunting )
- Get the fuck off of me ! - ( screaming and grunting )
- ( all screaming ) - Okay , okay !
Okay , okay , okay , okay !
- ( grunts ) - ( screams )
( screaming and crying )
Fuck you !
( Pat screams , cries ) Tiger : Oh , my God !
Keep it up ! Pull it up !
Oh fuck .
( Pat screams )
Yo , help me move the couch .
Reece : Help me move it !
Pat : Oh , shit !
- ( knocking ) - This will be over soon , gentlemen .
( metal music plays )
( Pat screaming )
I 'll fuckin ' crush you .
( screams )
( groans )
( shouts )
Reece : Get the box cutter !
Get the fucking box cutter out of his hand !
( Amber grunts )
( Big Justin grunts )
- Tell me when he 's out ! - Okay !
- ( Pat cries loudly ) - Tiger : Pat ! Pat !
Look at me , look at me , look at me .
Shush ! Shush !
Shush !
He 's out . He 's out !
- Oh , fuck . - ( groans )
Put pressure on it ! Put pressure !
I know , I know , I know .
Just breathe . Breathe . Breathe .
Sam : He 's not out !
He 's not out !
( gasping )
You got this ?
( cries )
How long does it take ...
until we know ... for sure ?
What the ...
Oh , Jesus .
Darcy : Any and all firearms ,
Clark will handle it from here on .
He give you an E.T.A. ?
You said no calls .
Right . Good .
- Phones too . - What happened in there ?
Darcy : Set Neal up for tomorrow
New drywall , pour a floor . Tell him we had a leak .
- Door with a frame , too . - What happened ?
Uh , a bit of a maelstrom tonight .
Visiting band hurt one of ours .
Daniel : Who ?
Emily .
Darcy : Maybe Big Justin , too .
What the fuck are we doing then ?
Let 's get in there .
We 're not coming apart is what we are doing .
We 're saving questions until this pig fuck is transferred off-site .
- ( dog barking ) - Darcy .
Okay . Last chance if anyone needs to take a leak .
- ( banging ) - ( Pat wailing )
( crashing )
I lost the gun .
You held on longer than I would have .
Hey .
I 'm going .
There 's no air shaft , there 's no sewer system ...
no nothing .
Tiger : There it is .
Sam : What time is it ?
It 's not daylight .
It 's something .
Out the way .
Tiger : Oh , fuck .
Look for a door .
Pat : Just let me know .
Hey ...
I 'm sorry about your friend .
- ( clanking ) - Reece : Shit !
Okay , move .
Tiger : Fuck !
( thumping )
Sam : Is there a lock ?
Other side , maybe .
We 're burning time .
Wait , but ...
Look ! There 's ... there 's ventilation !
Reece : Six inch ducts . Good luck .
Sam : Shouldn 't we look around more ?
Reece : We just did !
Go . Go , go . Push .
( creaking )
Amber : Heroin .
It 's not about her or us .
It 's a ... it 's a big ass bunker .
- Tiger : Give me your hand . - Reece : Big ass dead end .
Tiger : Give it to me . Hold it up , up , up .
- ( groans ) - All right . Look away , look away .
Maybe we can use this to our advantage .
Reece : We 're done .
I 'm done .
Okay ? You can close the door behind me if you want to strategize .
- We 're not ready ! - What do you think they 're doing out there ?
- That 's just it . We don 't know . - We fucking know
they mean us harm !
- ( groans ) - Sam : It 's just that if have guns ,
okay , why haven 't they mowed us down already ?
We can 't just go missing .
They need us found .
All right . Grab some shit
and get ready to run .
Then we die .
( Reece chuckles ) Yeah , but the longer we wait ,
the surer that is .
- Tiger , you ready ? - Tiger : Yeah , almost , man .
Pat : We can 't take it so seriously .
We gotta ...
treat this like paintball .
What ?
Rick Silva ...
helped organize the paintball for Skate-o 's bachelor party .
And we were short a few players to book the whole field ,
so they paired us up with these ex-Marines .
And the first few rounds , these guys just ...
tore us to shreds .
I mean , zero casualties on their side .
And I just cowered behind these trees
till I got shot .
Covered in paint . But Rick ...
Reece : Tiger , you done ?
Okay .
Pat , you 're done , too .
I 'm sorry , man . We gotta go .
That 's okay .
- Was that a pep talk ? - Tiger : Ready ?
( groans )
Reece : Now we won 't all live , but ...
I don 't know . Maybe we won 't all die .
- Here . - No , I 'm just gonna run .
Tiger : I got it .
All right , fuck it . Simon and Garfunkel .
Desert island band .
( breathes heavily )
Prince .
I , uh ...
- I 'm still the Misfits . - Reece : True school , man .
Are we going ?
Sam : Yeah .
Madonna and ... Slayer .
Here we go .
Watch it !
( metal music playing )
What the fuck ?
They 're letting us out .
Reece : How many exits are there ?
Uh , the main , the back , maybe the kitchen .
- I always ... - What about windows ?
See for yourselves .
( music stops abruptly )
Sam : Fuck .
Quiet .
( door closes )
Oh , shit .
Should we hide ?
Uh , whatever you want , man .
Sam : We ... we should split up .
Totally .
( thumping )
( dog snarling , barking )
Sam : What the fuck ?
Tiger !
( screams )
- Tiger ! - ( screams )
( dog chewing )
( Tiger groans )
Oh , shit , oh , shit .
Shit .
Oh , shit !
( groans )
Save it .
Oh , shit .
- ( dog snarling ) - ( gurgling , grunting )
( Sam breathing heavily )
( Sam screams )
( door closes )
( coughing )
Fass ! Fass !
Voran ! Fass !
Fass !
- ( dog snarling ) - ( screams )
( microphone feedback )
( dog whimpers )
( breathes heavily )
Hey .
They 're everywhere !
Where 's Reece ?
Pat : It 's us .
Come on . Move .
Sam , look .
Fleisch Wolf .
It 's a song .
It means " Meat Grinder . "
Clark : Up ! Up !
So ist 's brav .
You 're retiring him ?
Clark : He 's worked up .
Send in another .
Send two . Finish it .
Kill that feedback first .
And if I send in two fight dogs , what do you think they 'll do ?
Send me in there . I 'll finish up .
Just give me the rules .
All right .
Blades only .
Sloppy is fine .
Try not to hit the bone .
Okay .
Darcy : Take Jonathan .
Brute squad .
Keep him caged until we tag out .
He breathing ?
A little bit , yeah .
Let him bleed .
Later is better for time of death .
Keys ?
No .
( microphone feedback )
( feedback stops )
( footsteps , dragging )
They 're coming .
I can 't do this .
( banging )
Pat : Get back !
Sam : No !
Where 's Emily ?
What the fuck are you doing ?
Hey !
Which one did it ?
- Werm did it . - Daniel : Bullshit .
Which one ?
What did they tell you ?
What ? You want to know ?
You want him to know ?
Know what ?
Werm found out that she was leaving ...
but she didn 't say that it was with you .
" Meat Grinder . "
That song was their cue .
You should go .
Clark : Here we go .
This is taking too long .
Gabe ?
You didn 't want Daniel on door duty .
Why ?
Nothing concrete , he and ...
and Emily ...
Little lovebirds .
Recognize this ?
No , sir .
Of course not . You were still handing out
leaflets when these boys made their bones .
It 's from last Easter .
Supposed to disappear after the boot party .
He just started talking .
Amber 's alive saying Werm did it .
Never mind that .
You ...
Werm saved us all .
Sam ?
It 's okay .
I mean , it 's not okay .
- You didn 't know either ? - Pat : He 's with us .
Not where .
Pat : We gotta split .
This has a wider duct , I think .
Pat : We 're not gonna fit through there .
- ( shuffling ) - Sam : Oh !
Daniel , um , he can help .
Why ?
Who 's he ?
A traitor . If they don 't already know , they know now .
I can get us out of here .
Wow . A conspiracy .
No , just a cluster-fuck .
There is still blades and fangs for the visitors ,
but we are getting lean on time .
Now , if you have to shoot , shoot once .
If more than once , keep it a tight grouping
'cause you 'll be digging the slugs out yourself .
As for Daniel and Amber , they can ...
What did we forget ?
There 's a river on two sides . The quarry 's on another .
We can parallel the main road back , go for help .
Well , how do we get past the door ?
I know something you don 't .
Sam : Good . What ?
I know where we keep ...
- ( both scream ) - Too slow .
( all screaming )
( screams )
( grunts )
( grunting , gasping )
- ( dog barking ) - ( all scream )
Should we go ?
Now ?
We have the gun .
I guess .
Yes .
Sam : Yes !
Give me two .
( breathes heavily )
( all scream )
Easy ! Not her !
- ( man speaking German ) - Don 't fire !
Clark : Fass ! Fass !
- Fass ! - ( dog growls )
- ( screams ) - ( dog snarls )
Sam : Go !
Sam !
( Sam screams )
We 're never getting out .
Fuck .
( tape unwinding )
( breathes heavily )
( dog barking )
You know , I 'm lucky .
I guessed at least they were gonna shoot me .
( dog whimpering )
Three 'll do , gentlemen .
The fourth can disappear .
It 's time to start the clean-up .
I 'm gonna need a push broom .
This is supposed to have happened already .
- Time to sprint . - All : Yes , sir .
Darcy : Well done .
Thank him .
Nearly got away from me . Us .
Shouldn 't we be panicking ?
I 'm hungry .
I can 't die here with you .
So don 't .
You know , feel free just to ...
Hey , I want the rest of your pep talk .
Oh , no . It no longer applies .
Oh , come on .
I 'm curious .
It was paintballing ...
you were cowering ...
Yeah , Rick Silva .
We were getting slaughtered by these legit Iraq vets .
It totally applies .
Full camo , thousand-dollar automatic paintball guns .
They knew real war and they played real war .
Tactics , hand signals , flanking .
Just wiped us all out .
So Rick gets fed up and says , " Fuck it . "
Didn 't care about getting shot .
Didn 't care about taking cover .
It was hopeless , man .
So the last match , the whistle blows ,
and he just tears out there ,
full jackass , in ... in sneakers and cut-offs
and he ... wipes out their whole team .
Doesn 't stop .
Just keeps running and laughing and shooting ...
until they 're all dead .
Pretend dead .
And we 're up against real guns .
Yeah .
Either way , we can 't play real war .
Let 's pretend .
For you .
We 're just mopping up tonight .
You already earned these .
Maybe push Neal , depending on the mess ,
to start looking for a new house band .
We 've really gotta get back to a routine .
You think Cowcatcher 's gonna talk ?
I 'm more worried about their habits .
Really have to stay away from that nigger dope .
There 's a bad batch doing the rounds .
( van buzzes )
( engine starts )
We 're good to go .
We 're set .
Darcy : This all hinges on nothing having happened here .
Now , let 's be clear .
Clark : This should keep him alive for another hour .
I would consider it a personal favor
if he dies with meat in his teeth .
- Come on . Come on . - ( dog whimpers )
Bite command is " fass . "
It 's all you 'll need .
Disregard . Just shoot who is left .
They don 't have to be accounted for .
Forensics is no longer a concern .
We call this in late , all is for naught .
You guys got any 12 gauge ?
Not in the office . Try the bar .
- How many shots you have left ? - Kyle : Three .
So you have one extra .
No shells .
Jonathan : Behind the bar . Better get started .
- ( microphone feedback ) - Shit !
( dog barks )
Jonathan : Easy ! Easy !
Easy !
- ( dog whimpers ) - No buckshot !
Gabe : What 's happening ?
Dog freaked . And turn this shit off !
I tried ! It 's not coming from our mixer .
Go ! We got this .
And don 't tell Darcy . Or Clark .
- We going ? - Yeah .
Hey !
Pat : Down there , you dip-shit fashion punk clown motherfuckers !
- Turn around ! - Pat : Shazbot !
What ? What ... Who is that ?
Odin himself .
( grunts , screams )
( microphone feedback stops )
( screams )
Give me the shotgun .
No , I got the shotgun .
Then you go down this fucking hole .
Three shots ?
Yeah .
You hear me fire twice , you come down no matter what .
- This is a trap . - Yeah , no shit .
You wanna go tell Darcy ?
He 's gonna be pissed .
Watch my back .
Fuck this .
Get Gabe , man !
We need two down here and one up there .
Who 's got the nine ? - I think Alan does , but I 'm not sure ...
- ( Amber screams ) - Oh , fuck ! Block it !
Amber : Pat !
He 's got three shots left !
Bitch .
Gabe !
( power washer )
Pat : Amber !
Yeah ?
Uh ...
never mind !
Amber : Two shots left !
Nice fuckin ' try !
( grunts )
Go fuck yourself !
Shit . Shit .
Oh , shit !
Amber : Pat !
One shot left !
Fuck .
Zero .
Oh , shit !
( both grunting )
Get off of me !
Got him .
Totally .
Flabbergasted that motherfucker .
If I had any idea ...
Amber : Anymore dogs ?
People ?
No . Not here .
They 're ... up the road .
I don 't want to go to jail .
Does anyone know how to hotwire a car ?
No .
I 'd stay off the road anyway .
( chain dragging )
Are you gonna shoot me ?
Where 's Werm ?
- We sent him home ... - Stay quiet till we 're out .
( distant gunshot )
( dog barking )
- It 's the residents . - ( distant gunshot )
What are they doing ?
Something you don 't want to see .
We can call the cops when we get to the orchard .
Did you see them die ?
Two .
Not the third .
I think I 'm going .
You can call the cops when you get there .
If you disappear , I 'll find you .
I will .
I promise .
You should go , too .
Just hedge our bets .
You got three rounds ...
and I 've seen you pump a shotgun .
( sighs ) Fair enough .
Do you believe him ?
- Shh . - ( dog barking )
- ( barking continues ) - ( Clark speaking German )
Nimm futter !
( dog growls )
Clark : Nimm futter !
Nimm futter ! Nimm futter !
- Alan : Jesus . - Nimm futter !
Alan : That ought to be enough .
Clark : Lass es ! Lass es !
- Lass es ! - ( dog barks )
So ist 's brav .
Aus . Aus .
Wipe it down !
( car engine starts )
Do you think they 'd leave the engine on ?
Clark : Yeah . It 'll run the gauge down too .
Let 's call this in .
Aus . Aus .
You got the dog ?
I got the dog .
Tie him up .
Give me your gun .
I don 't have one .
I 'll shoot you either way if you don 't hand me one .
Throw it .
( dog barking )
They 're making it our fault .
You were trespassing .
Pat : It looks fishy to me .
The cloth is to make it seal .
I wouldn 't do it like that .
They got my gun .
- Shut up . - Clark : Listen ...
( chain dragging )
So we 're doing that ?
Why else would we walk up here ?
Pat : I don 't know . And I was gonna ...
ruin the crime scene .
Oh .
I thought we 'd leave a new one .
This ...
is a nightmare .
For us all .
Tell me those stupid fucking words are his last .
Do you have a phone ?
It 's funny .
You were so scary at night .
( grunts )
We need the police .
( TV plays )
Tad on radio : Okay , I 'm the Ain 't Rights from Washington , D.C.
Sam on radio : Uh , technically , we 're from Arlington .
Tad on radio : Nice . Uh , and this is for Seaside HCFM .
( chain dragging )
Reece on radio : Yeah , if we can afford it .
Tad on radio : Yeah , no , I really dig the analogue style .
Uh , which brings me to the fact that you guys are hard to find .
( chain dragging )
( guns clicking )
I know what it is .
What what is ?
My desert island band .
Tell somebody who gives a shit .
( rock music plays )
♪ When the sky is gray ♪
♪ And the moon is hate ♪
♪ I 'll be down to get you ♪
♪ Roots of earth will shake ♪
♪ Sinister purpose ♪
♪ Knockin ' at your door ♪
♪ Come and take my hand ♪
♪ Burn away the goodness ♪
♪ You and I remain ♪
♪ Did you see the last war ? ♪
♪ Well , here I am again ♪
♪ Sinister purpose ♪
♪ Knockin ' at your door ♪
♪ Come and take my hand ♪
♪ I can set you free ♪
♪ Make you rich and wise ♪
♪ We can live forever ♪
♪ Look into my eyes ♪
♪ Sinister purpose ♪
♪ Knockin ' at your door ♪
♪ Come and take my hand ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm ♪
( punk music plays )
♪ You can 't disappear anymore ♪
♪ I see your face lurking outside the window ♪
♪ You say you 're a trife , I 'm a bore ♪
♪ You touch yourself , Put your face in the pillow ♪
♪ But the funny thing about you is ♪
♪ You remembered to leave it behind ♪
♪ And the funny thing about me is ♪
♪ I 'm a member of the Right Brigade ♪
♪ Makes no difference to me what side you choose ♪
♪ What side will lose ♪
♪ All there is to perceive is what I want ♪
♪ And I know how to get it ♪
♪ But the funny thing about you is ♪
♪ You remembered to leave it behind ♪
♪ And the funny thing about me is ♪
♪ I 'm a member of the Right ♪
♪ Right Brigade ♪
( dramatic score playing )